♪ Pink hands so fine ♪
♪ Gold-branded wine ♪
♪ Spring paints willows green;
palace walls can't confine ♪
♪ East wind unfair ♪
♪ Happy times rare ♪
♪ In my heart, sad thoughts throng ♪
♪ We've severed for years long ♪
♪ Wrong, wrong, wrong ♪
Si Jin
Episode 8
Years ago, a fortune-teller
once declared me ill-fated,
destined to bring calamity upon my family.
Fearing implication and loss of favor,
she devised a scheme
to convince my father
to send me away,
just like that.
(In the past, )
(he seldom spoke of his past.)
(All I knew was his kin's disdain)
(that exiled him to guard the borders.)
(I never imagined)
(he shared a fate similar to mine, )
(branded an ill omen)
(from our birth.)
But what if that fortune-teller
was a fraud,
spouting doom just to
seek fame and fortune?
So what if he's a fraud?
There's no point
in digging deeper now.
Ultimately,
the decision
lies with our parents.
You think it's pointless,
but I think
it is necessary.
If the vulnerable
are saddled
with all sorts of false charges
by people in the world
without question
or resistance,
doesn't that
validate the wicked's lies
and make themselves accomplices?
If you were
falsely accused,
would you seek justice?
If it were me,
I would make
the accuser pay.
Mr. Yu,
after all these years,
don't you want to know the truth?
One Capital Security Office,
two people giving me a headache.
But who reported the buried bodies
at the Marquis's Mansion?
It was the fourth daughter
of Earl Dongping's household,
Jiang Si.
Cao Xingyu
is her second sister's husband.
That day,
the second daughter of the Jiang Family
invited her sisters to
the Marquis's Mansion.
Late that night, Jiang Si, sleepless,
went to the garden
and stumbled upon servants burying a body.
She reported it
to the Capital Security.
But later,
Cao Xingyu, the villain, struck first,
accusing his wife
of ordering the killing.
Jiang Si
then came forward to testify.
is no ordinary soul,
daring to cross Marquis Changxing.
Each bolder than the last,
none of them are ordinary.
Thank...
Thank you, Your Majesty.
(Grand Princess's Mansion)
Your Highness,
the Speed Guards
have mentioned Cao Xingyu
for collaborating with Nanwu.
Luckily,
His Majesty didn't bring it up this time.
So
I guess it's over.
My brother's mind
is a labyrinth of thoughts.
He keeps everything bottled up,
which will only lead to disaster.
Your Majesty,
I have seized all documents
related to the Surreal Wander
(Two bottles of Surreal Wander)
and Nanwu
from Marquis Changxing's Mansion.
Put them away.
Don't mention it again.
Your Majesty, knowing well something's wrong,
you set it aside for now.
What is your intention behind this?
Nanwu spies seep through every crack,
their infiltration so deep
it chills the bone.
They'll inevitably scheme
to ensnare the pillars of our court.
We have to be on our guard.
The Crown Prince is here!
Your son kneels in contrition, Father.
Prince Qi is here!
The 1st and 3rd Princes are here!
The 5th Prince is here!
The 6th and 8th Princes are here!
Your sons kneel in contrition, Father.
Why did you come so late
to kneel in contrition?
(Yu Lang, Crown Prince)
Father, though I had
a few encounters with Marquis Changxing's,
no, Cao Xingyu, the criminal,
our acquaintance was merely superficial.
I truly had no knowledge
of his murderous deeds.
Father, Marquis Changxing has been
(Yu Zhang, Prince Qi)
at odds with me,
but Ling'an hasn't witnessed
such a heinous murder in decades.
Your personal trial of Cao Xingyu
has been universally praised by the people.
Father is wise.
Turns out you're all here
for Cao Xingyu's case.
All right, all rise.
Thank you, Father.
Since you're all here,
I'd like to ask you
if you think
I'm usually
too strict with you.
Yu Lang, you tell me.
Father,
your strictness towards me
is for my own good
and to secure the realm's future.
So you think I'm strict?
No, no.
No, you're not.
You're so scared.
Yu Zhang, you tell me.
Father,
as princes
supported by the people,
we must be strict with ourselves.
All right. Stop.
You're not answering the question.
I have eight sons and six daughters.
With busy government affairs,
I don't have much energy
to teach most of you.
Of course,
Yu Lang is the crown prince.
I'm naturally more strict with him.
If you have
anything to say,
speak freely tonight.
Don't hold it back.
People holding their feelings in for too long
will inevitably lose their rationality
and come up with devious ways
to relieve their emotions.
Do you understand?
We will follow your instructions.
Still, there is one missing.
Your Majesty,
it's windy today.
(Tiande Hall)
Please return to your chamber.
Your Majesty, in your wisdom,
know that Zhang and I are innocent.
Do not penalize us
because of Qi.
The ministers say
he brought disaster to Dazhou.
Then send him away,
(Consort Xian, Yu Qi's birth mother)
away from
the Imperial City and Dazhou.
Qi is the child you carried for ten months.
Can you bear to part with him?
Even if I can't, what can I do?
He was fated
with ill omen from his first breath.
Qi was sent to the South
in swaddling clothes.
Left on the war-torn frontiers
to grow up alone without his parents,
who knows what he's become.
The boy is wayward.
Every time Cui Xu went on an inspection tour,
I sent him to check on him,
but he always avoided meeting him.
He must hold a grudge against me.
Your Majesty,
if you miss the 7th Prince,
why not summon him back to Ling'an?
The Nanwu uprising
that began with his birth
has yet to be quelled.
With the Nightingale Division's shadow
creeping across Dazhou these past years,
his return will make him
the target of public criticism again.
However, Your Majesty,
the 7th Prince
has inherited your valor in battle,
leading the Chiyu Cavalry
to countless victories.
Does this not prove
he is no foe
to the country?
It's not time yet.
I need to think about it.
Chief.
What are you looking at?
Go investigate the Directorate of Astronomy.
Haven't you
been reluctant to look into
what happened back then?
I've changed my mind.
I want to know
who framed me.
Miss Chi,
this is the busiest street in town.
Yes.
Look at this shop, Miss Jiang.
It's been in business for years.
It's very famous.
A snack spot up ahead is famous too.
Miss Chi, how's the location
of this shop?
(Qiaoxiang Shop)
With so many shops around,
opening a shop here
ensures a steady stream of customers.
I think so too.
Once I get the shop up and running,
(Qiaoxiang Shop)
I'll need all hands on deck.
Miss Chi,
I find you smart and resourceful.
Would you consider joining me?
Miss Jiang,
you've already saved me from dire straits.
I don't know
how to repay you.
Now you extend another generous offer,
but I can't be in your debt.
What are your plans then?
I plan to return home
and start a school in the countryside
to teach girls who cannot afford education
literacy and reason.
I'll teach them not to be
as muddle-headed as I used to be.
I hope they will be like you,
who aspire to hearts holding vast horizons
and eyes perceiving greater justice.
I'm flattered.
Miss Chi,
your past sufferings are over.
Every day
will be a new beginning.
Thank you, Miss Jiang.
Take care.
(Qiaoxiang Shop)
Stay safe on the way.
Miss Si.
Take care.
♪ The cool breeze comes and goes ♪
♪ I dare to love and hate ♪
Let's go.
♪ Ask the day and the night ♪
♪ If they saw a glimmer fall and take root ♪
♪ Growing between us ♪
♪ And breeding love ♪
♪ Smile at each other for the future ♪
♪ In the end, we're still together ♪
♪ Like shadows ♪
Remember,
Heaven helps those who help themselves
and abandons those who abandon themselves.
♪ Our bond trickles down from youth ♪
♪ Time glows ♪
♪ Together, we'll see light ♪
♪ And stars ♪
(Morning Drizzle)
(Haitang Chamber)
Father.
Si, you're home.
Zhan.
Father,
what are you doing?
Airing out books and paintings?
I heard from your brother
that you want to buy a shop.
Father,
these are your lifelong collections.
How can you just pawn them off?
I'll find a way to buy the shop.
What can an unmarried girl like you
possibly do?
Father, here's my plan.
I will
rent the shop first.
It won't cost much.
Then I'll use
some of my dowry Mother left me,
and that should be enough.
Once the business picks up,
I'll buy the shop.
No renting. Buy it directly.
If my daughter wants to start a business,
shouldn't her father
buy her a shop?
Keep the dowry your mother left you.
You need financial security to stand tall.
Besides, I just
followed rich young lords' trends
when buying these calligraphy works
and paintings.
I haven't
cared for them in years.
Your brother's collections are even more
flashy without substance.
(Haitang Chamber)
He was excited for days
and then threw them in the study
without even looking at them for years.
Look at this dust!
Exactly.
Before buying,
they seemed like rare treasures;
once home,
just some trinkets.
Si, do me a favor.
You know what,
my study is a mess and can barely squeeze in.
Zhan,
Father.
Enough, come help now.
Your brother is clumsy.
If he breaks anything,
we won't get a good price.
Father,
are you really that sure
I can run this shop well?
Of course.
Don't forget
your grandpa was Lingshui's richest man.
Business sense
is an inherited gift
in your bloodline.
Father,
all I do is eat, drink, and be merry.
So my blood of mine
must have come from you, right?
Scram.
Didn't I tell you
I picked you up from somewhere?
Seriously?
No wonder you've been so awful to me.
By the way, Si,
you mustn't let your grandma
find out about your business venture.
Like most Ling'an folk,
she looks down
on merchants,
and would never allow the Earl's
legitimate daughter to engage in trade.
Understood?
I understand.
Father,
see how effective
this Yunxiang Herb is.
The books
show no insect damage
after a full year,
still perfectly intact.
My daughter knows so much.
By the way, Father,
I've rarely heard you mention
the Directorate of Astronomy.
And you seldom associate
with your former colleagues either.
Since your mother's passing,
I've lost the heart for official duties,
so I resigned from my post.
I've always thought
reading the night skies
is mysterious,
predicting weather
and divining fortunes.
While celestial study
holds endless wonders,
the Directorate of Astronomy
is not just about astronomy and geography.
There are more
social climbers
and forced compromises.
Father,
do you recall those copybooks
you kept drilling me on as a child?
Look,
this one slipped through the cracks.
I vividly recall these copybooks.
Back then,
every time I bought one,
it would go missing.
It was strange.
I threw them all away secretly.
I threw a lot away for you.
No wonder your handwriting
is pure chicken scratch.
This isn't for sale.
Drill those strokes.
No, I'll sell this one first.
Ji, hurry up.
- Sell this copybook first!
- Stop there!
You can't sell it.
If you sell it,
you'll face month-long house arrest.
Don't sell it!
Stop right there!
(Fragrance Shop)
Miss,
no one is willing
(Fragrance Shop)
to come and help in our shop.
Ling'an women all balk
at being called businesswomen.
The opening day is looming,
but we're still short of staff.
What should we do?
Miss Chuchu!
Chuchu.
Jiang Zhan told me
you're hiring,
so I brought a candidate.
(Rou'er)
Miss Jiang, how do you do?
Miss Jiang, congratulations
on your new shop's opening.
How do you do?
Chuchu,
you've truly saved me in my hour of need.
Rest assured, Rou'er is definitely reliable.
She's from my hometown,
once a rouge shop owner herself.
Chief, after cracking the case
with His Majesty's backing,
sycophants are eager to curry favor with us.
Mr. Zhao from the Grand Council...
No. I'm busy.
Yes.
Mr. Yu.
- Mr. Jiang.
- What a coincidence.
- Are you rich?
- Come on.
You bought so much stuff.
My sister's fragrance shop
opens the day after tomorrow.
I bought her some opening gifts.
Fragrance shop?
Perfect timing.
I was going to deliver your invitation.
Be sure to come support the opening.
I'm sorry, but he isn't available that day.
I am.
I'll adjust my schedule.
I'll come, definitely.
That's good.
Fragrance Shop?
Good name.
Long Dan!
What's up, sir?
Where did you put it?
Where did I put what?
Where did you put the thing
I asked you to get?
You didn't ask me to get anything.
Where's my bronze mirror?
Where did you put it?
We don't have a bronze mirror.
Go borrow one from the neighbor.
- Go, go, go!
- I have to...
Chief. Chief.
Mirror, mirror.
The mirror is here.
- Take it easy.
- Here.
Chief, you're dressed like this
to meet Miss Jiang?
What do you think?
With such...
With such striking poise,
you're sure
to impress her.
Haven't I always been like this?
Sure, sure.
Ring the gong, prosper the business.
Grand opening,
great fortune.
Mirror the heart for clarity.
Act with integrity, discipline strictly.
Subtle scents through seasons;
fragrant trails on every journey.
Gourds displayed,
fortune conveyed.
New business, thriving fortunes.
Look how handsome
those gentlemen are.
Mr. Yu, not bad.
You look dashing today.
- Mr. Zhen, thank you for coming.
- Jiang...
Thank you.
Mr. Zhen, don't you always advocate
unwavering duty
and attendance on official leave?
Yes.
But Miss Jiang
personally delivered the invitation
to my door yesterday.
With such an honor,
you know I can't possibly decline.
Thanks a lot.
Really?
Why?
Didn't you receive
Miss Jiang's invitation?
Of course I did.
That's why I'm here.
Before she had the chance to deliver it,
we happened to meet on the road,
so it saved her the trouble
of making a trip.
I see.
What a coincidence.
Chief, didn't you say Jiang Zhan...
Miss Jiang, prepare for the unveiling.
(Fragrance Shop)
Great!
- Great!
- Bravo!
Share fragrance, gather blessings.
Perfect!
Here, one for each.
- It's all inside.
- Take a look inside.
Come in and take a look.
Thanks for coming and supporting us.
Come on inside.
Have a look inside.
- Come on.
- One for each.
Is this yours?
- Thanks.
- Thanks a lot.
Have a look inside, guys.
Come on.
- Si.
- Have a look inside.
- Come on in.
Good luck with your business.
(Wealth from all directions)
Come on in.
Thanks, Zhan.
Miss Jiang.
Congratulations on your opening.
(Auspicious opening, customers surge)
Thanks, Mr. Zhen.
Miss Jiang!
May your business thrive and prosper.
Thank you, Mr. Yu.
Today, our opening
is honored by your presence.
We specially prepared 100 red vouchers
to grant you half-price access.
Anyone who spends 20 taels or more
gets a Duck Incense Burner.
Come on in, please.
- That's great.
- Come on.
Jiang Si, this is my congratulatory gift.
Chuchu, you've helped me a lot today
and even got me a gift.
I carved this myself.
It's a talisman, proven powerful.
What a cute little horse!
Little horse!
- Jiang Zhan!
- Did you make this?
Who knew you had
such a hidden skill?
Give it back. It's for Jiang Si.
My sister is busy.
Why don't I keep it for her?
Give it back.
Miss, you're amazing.
Just the scents of monthly perfumes
are enough to pique everyone's curiosity.
This is just the beginning.
When we debut limited-edition perfumes
one after another,
the real game begins.
Ji, Long Dan, come and help!
Coming.
Everyone.
Aman, take it easy.
Miss Jiang, you have affection and faith,
courage and wit.
Independently,
you've opened such a big fragrance shop.
I truly admire you.
I'm flattered, Mr. Zhen.
Miss Jiang,
would you please introduce
these perfumes?
These are gentlemen's perfumes.
For gentlemen's perfumes,
I substituted florals
with mint, cedar,
ebony, and eaglewood,
essences long cherished
by refined scholars,
most befitting your eminences.
Remarkable,
truly remarkable!
Miss Jiang is ingenious
to come up with such a brilliant idea.
Allow me
to introduce the perfumes.
This one is called Autumn Grove,
crafted with citrus, ebony,
amber, and other spices.
Its rich and generous aroma
mirrors modest scholars' unbound spirit,
particularly befitting Mr. Yu.
Mr. Yu,
this bottle of perfume is for you.
Thank you, Miss.
As a mere martial artist,
I don't do perfumes.
Don't waste it.
Then allow me to present another one.
This one is crafted
with ebony, eaglewood,
(Scrolls Slumber)
bergamot, and angelica.
Its calming fragrance
crystallizes the mind.
It's called Scrolls Slumber.
Mr. Zhen,
this one suits you very well.
Please accept it.
Thank you, Miss Jiang.
Scrolls Slumber.
What a good name.
Looks like
you know me well.
Let me see.
It's a good name, indeed.
I never had the habit of using perfume,
but your words convinced me.
(Autumn Grove)
I might as well try both.
Perfect.
Unbelievable.
Miss,
the perfumes over there are sold out.
I need to get some more.
All sold out?
Ok, go get more.
Yes.
Take a whiff.
Do you feel
the gallop across endless grasslands,
wind roaring
past your ears?
So many perfumes.
Can you remember all their names?
This is Wanderer's Odyssey.
Unfettered grace and swift reckonings.
That sounds perfect for me.
I think this one suits you better.
What's this?
Warm Sun.
It suits you.
I am
the warm sun?
(Haitang Chamber)
Si.
Father,
you're here.
First day of business.
Tired?
Looks like you're doing well.
Your grin is splitting your face.
Father, you're making fun of me again.
Look what I brought you.
What?
Milk Cakes!
There's more.
Spring tea.
Father knows me best.
Spring tea paired with Milk Cakes,
- ultimate treat of Ling'an.
- Ultimate treat of Ling'an.
Tasty.
Si,
I didn't give you enough care.
Now you have to
hold up this family alone.
It's too much for you.
Father, now I'm doing
all the things I like.
I'm happy.
I know.
My daughter is the most capable.
That's right.
By the way,
I was going to tell you
a few words,
but seeing that you were busy,
I never got the chance to say them.
What is it, Father?
What do you think
about your second sister?
She has been ill-fated in love.
Luck hasn't been on her side.
We can't control
our luck,
but when
misfortune strikes,
we can still choose wisely.
If your future husband treats you badly,
never mind whatever the impact
it may have on your in-laws or us,
come home at once.
Yes, Father.
But I don't want to
get married yet.
Don't marry unless you're ready.
I'm not pushing you.
Life is too long
for a half-hearted union.
You know,
finding someone who truly stirs your soul
is rare magic.
I want my daughter
to meet such a man.
Of course,
he must feel the same
for my daughter.
Otherwise, I won't give my consent.
Your daughter asks for nothing more.
There is
no greater happiness
than living a peaceful life
with my father and brother.
Having the whole family together
is better than anything else.
These are your favorites.
Sit down.
Thank you, Mother.
You're the best cook.
(Mrs. Zhen)
Heng,
you keep
skipping meals.
I think you've
lost weight again lately.
The caseload has been crushing lately.
Once I'm done with it,
everything will be fine.
I mean it's about time
you get a wife
to remind you to eat regularly.
Don't bother.
Look at my days,
swamped with official duties.
My time has
stretched thin already.
Register of Brides-to-Be.
I realize that your ability
to gather information
is almost as good as ours.
You know what,
I paid a lot of money for this
at the Matchmaker's Hall.
Since you paid so much money,
I will
read it carefully later.
I don't believe you.
Read it now.
Whichever girl you're interested in,
leave it to me.
(Fragrance Shop)
(Jade Bloom Aroma)
I'll take this one.
Ok, here you are.
Here, take a look.
Rou'er, here.
- Ok.
- Have a cup of tea.
Take a break.
Miss, have some tea.
Chuchu.
Come here.
You've been busy today.
Have some tea.
This tea smells good.
It's jasmine tea.
How is it today?
Jiang Si,
you know what,
your perfumes are amazing.
Every perfume here
transports me
to a different world.
When I paint the visions in my mind
for our customers,
they reach for their wallets every time.
Fragrance Shop?
I've never seen you
use these before.
Well,
a new fragrance shop
opened in town lately.
I went there to take a look.
The shopkeeper said
this perfume can refresh my mind,
so I bought it to try.
Scrolls Slumber?
To refresh your mind?
I could be mistaken, probably.
Tell me.
Who did you buy this for?
I bought it for myself.
Which girl?
Mother,
it doesn't involve any girl.
I know my son best.
How dare I lie to you?
If you don't tell me, I'll be angry.
Fine, it's Jiang Si,
fourth daughter of Earl Dongping's household.
We just know each other.
That's all.
She is the owner
of Fragrance Shop.
(The same Jiang Si who set the city abuzz)
(by breaking her engagement?)
(Fragrance Shop)
Fragrance Shop.
While other shops
deploy pretty girls
to coax customers,
we neither
coax nor grovel.
It will help us to earn gentlemen's respect.
Then, they'll be more convinced
by the visions you paint.
Miss,
could you recommend some fragrances?
Chuchu,
I'll do it. You take a break.
What kind of fragrance would you like?
Used for gifts.
My niece
is visiting soon.
I'll prepare two welcome gifts for her.
She is
about your age.
Allow me to recommend some to you.
You can try this one first.
This is Angelica Balm.
Apply it
to your wrists and behind your ears.
As your body warmth activates it,
the fragrance will diffuse
through your garments.
It's elegant.
Do you have any other aromas?
You can try this one too.
This balm
is crafted with lychee rind
blended into fruit notes.
It's always raining
this time of year in Ling'an.
(Fragrance)
Fresh and elegant.
Thank you for your recommendation.
I'll take both.
Would you like to see more?
I will come again.
Thank you, Ma'am.
Ma'am.
Please wait.
Ma'am,
(Fragrance Shop)
you forgot your wallet.
I'm so forgetful.
Thank you, Miss.
You're welcome.
You're a beautiful girl with a kind heart.
I'm flattered, Ma'am.
Qi, what are you doing here?
Why don't you get in?
Why is Mrs. Zhen here?
Mr. Zhen's mother?
It's her.
No wonder
she seems to
like Jiang Si very much.
She dismissed others' recommendations
without a glance,
yet listened carefully
to Jiang Si's every word.
I get the sense she's not here for perfumes.
Instead, she seems to come to see Jiang Si.
Qi, do you think
she is here to check out
a potential daughter-in-law?
No way.
Definitely not.
Take care, Ma'am.
Come back again.
Mr. Yu!
Miss Jiang, you're here.
What are you doing here, Mr. Yu?
Are you going on a case?
No, I was just passing by
and brought some food for my sister.
I, this...
Go ahead.
Wash it before eating.
I've washed it.
Wash it well.
I...
How careless she is!
Mr. Yu,
as a martial artist,
do you wear Autumn Grove too?
Martial artists love Autumn.
It's summer.
Mr. Yu, wait a minute.
(Invitation)
I was planning
to visit your residence today.
My grandma's birthday is coming soon.
On behalf of Earl Dongping's Mansion,
I cordially invite you
to attend her celebration banquet.
Thank you, Mr. Yu,
for all your previous assistance.
Ok, I'll be there.
Wait.
Sit down, honey.
Thank you, darling.
What would you like to drink?
It's scorching today.
Get us some cold tea, will you?
- Yes.
- Wait.
No cold drinks for her cold constitution.
Floral tea would be better.
That's her favorite.
Yes.
(Zhu Ziyu, Jiang Yi's husband)
Look at you, all sweaty.
You don't always have to indulge me.
No worries.
The journey must have
worn you out, darling.
Visiting your parents' home is a rare joy,
no hardship at all.
Because your safety and happiness
are my greatest wish.
Here's your tea!
Thank you.
Enjoy your tea.
By the way,
tomorrow is your grandma's birthday.
When you see your elder sister,
talk to her.
Ask her
how she's been getting along lately.
Yes, Father.
I miss her too.
I've failed
your eldest sister.
When she was born,
I was young and my world
revolved around your mother.
I had little
left for her.
She has been nothing
but thoughtful and capable
and never demanded more than I could give.
Thankfully,
she married well.
Her husband
is good-natured
who treasures her.
Don't worry, Father.
She is so kind-hearted.
She will surely lead a good life.
All right, I'm leaving.
Take care, Father.
(Capital Security Office)
Mother, why are you here?
Heng,
I brought you a new gown.
What's the occasion?
I hear today is the birthday
of the old lady of Earl Dongping's Mansion.
You'll go with me
to pay our respects.
Oh?
You have a great eye.
I also like the fourth young lady
of the family.
Mother,
since when did you know her?
Enough dilly-dallying.
Go try it on.
Quickly.
(Earl Dongping's Mansion, Jiang)
Miss,
what's the hurry to get to the main hall?
Today is Grandma's birthday banquet,
and Mother is busy making arrangements.
I must do a good job
so that Mother
will stop being mad at me
over what happened to Qian
and focus on arranging me
a good marriage.
Miss, you're quick-witted as always.
Right?
- Hurry up.
- Yes.
Watch out, Miss.
Miss, are you all right?
Are you Mr. Zhen?
Yes, I am.
What a pretty young lady.
We're here
to celebrate Mrs. Jiang's birthday.
Grandma should be
in the backyard right now.
Are you her granddaughter?
You're beautiful and kind-hearted.
I'm flattered, Mrs. Zhen.
Mr. Zhen,
may I show you the way?
Thank you, Miss.
This way, please.
Why hasn't Yi come yet?
Is her husband preventing her from coming?
We haven't seen her in ages.
Today is Grandma's birthday.
(Earl Dongping's Mansion)
She must come.
The Zhu Family has no reason to stop her.
Exactly.
Lingshui is a long way from Ling'an.
Let's wait a little longer.
Si, Zhan.
Yi.
It's Yi.
Si.
Yi.
Yi!
(It's good to see her)
(again.)
You must have suffered.
Last time when you
broke off your engagement,
I couldn't make it back to support you.
It's all my fault.
You don't blame me, right?
It's ok, Yi.
I just miss you so much.
I miss you too.
I'm always worried you're not doing well.
But seeing that
you look great,
I can finally feel at ease.
You two are so close.
Yi always talks about you at home.
Before coming back for Grandma's birthday,
she started preparing gifts
half a month in advance.
(The End of Episode 8)
♪ From place to place ♪
♪ I drift in the world alone ♪
♪ The cool breeze comes and goes ♪
♪ I dare to love and hate ♪
♪ Ask the day and the night ♪
♪ If they saw a glimmer fall and take root ♪
♪ Growing between us ♪
♪ And breeding love ♪
♪ Smile at each other for the future ♪
♪ In the end, we're still together ♪
♪ Like shadows ♪
♪ We're brave enough to advance together ♪
♪ We promise each other the future ♪
♪ Our bond trickles down from youth ♪
♪ Time glows ♪
♪ Together, we'll see light ♪
♪ And stars ♪
♪ Don't ask what our fate is ♪
♪ Let life carve the growth rings ♪
♪ We'll reach the end eventually ♪
♪ All will bloom in spring ♪
♪ We promise each other the future ♪
♪ Our bond trickles down from youth ♪
♪ Time glows ♪
♪ Together, we'll see light ♪
♪ Smile at each other for the future ♪
♪ We travel at night in the cold ♪
♪ The moonlight shines like water ♪
♪ Those in love will have sweet dreams ♪
♪ Cherish each other in the future ♪
♪ Time goes by, but memories remain ♪
♪ Take a look to remember everything ♪
♪ We will see flowers fill the city again ♪